getwebcake.com 2014-10-29

# WebCake - Privacy Policy

## WEBCAKE PRIVACY POLICY

#### _Last updated: July 11, 2013_

### 1\. INTRODUCTION

This Privacy Policy is part of the WebCake (the "Company", "we" or "us") End User License Agreement available at License Agreement, and applies to all users of the WebCake toolbar software (the "Software"). The Software is supported by advertising (including search, banner, text link, transitional, interstitial and full page), which is not associated with or endorsed by any underlying websites. 

This Privacy Policy describes the collection and use of Software users' personal information (e.g., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name and address), and non-personally identifiable information (e.g., interests, demographics and site usage) to the extent such information is associated with a particular user. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us immediately at the email address in the last paragraph below. 

### 2\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

#### User Submitted Information

When contacting us, you may submit personal information (such as your full name and other identifying information) to allow us to effectively respond to your inquiry. Your submission is voluntary and you have the choice not to disclose any information to us. Your user submitted information may also include user names associated with third party services, information or content you have permitted third parties to share with the Company, and any information you have made public in connection with third party services. In addition, the Company may supplement user submitted information with other information collected or obtained from third parties. 

#### Collected Information

**Accessing and Using the Software.** When using the Software, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected, stored and used for business and marketing purposes, such as maintaining and improving the Software, conducting research, and displaying more relevant advertisements. Such information may be transferred to servers that are located in the United States for these purposes. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation: IP address, unique identifier number, operating system, browser information, URLs visited, pages viewed, search queries entered, and other software and hardware information. This collected data may also be supplemented with information obtained from third parties or submitted by users. 

**Tracking and Data Collection Technologies.** The Company may use browser cookies, web and DOM storage data, Adobe Flash cookies, pixels, beacons, and other tracking and data collection technologies, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. These technologies may be used to collect and store information about your use of the Software while browsing websites, including without limitation, web pages, features and content you have accessed, search queries you have run, referral URL information, links you have clicked on, and advertisements you have seen. This data is used for business purposes such as providing more relevant ads and content, and market research. The Company may also use these technologies and other similar tools to relate your use of the Software to personal information obtained from you or a reputable third party. For example, cookie, click stream or other data about your activities using the Software may allow us to refine the ads, offers and content provided to you through the Software to items we think you will find interesting and relevant to you, based on your prior online activities and preferences. 

**Third Party Tracking and Data Collection.** Third parties that support the Software by serving advertisements or providing other services, such as tracking aggregate site usage or providing users with the ability to comment on or share content, may also use cookies, pixels and other tracking and data collection technologies described above to collect user information. The Company does not control these third parties and their use of these technologies is governed by the privacy policies of the third parties using such technologies. 

For more information about third party ad networks that use these technologies, see <http://www.aboutads.info/>. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g., [ http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies ](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies) ). 

Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe's website at the following link - [ http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html ](http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html) . 

Please note that blocking cookies or implementing other restrictions may interfere with the normal operation of the Software. 

### 3\. USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We only share your non-public personal information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy. In addition, the Company may share your personal information with our parent, subsidiary or affiliate companies without restriction. 

Any information about users that we collect or receive may be used and shared for the following purposes: 

**To provide and manage the Software.** We use the information we collect from and receive about users to provide the Software to you, to measure and improve the Software, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content, advertising, and marketing messages, and to provide you with customer support and respond to inquiries. We may use aggregated, anonymous data about use of and activity on the Software to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy. 

**To allow third party service providers to assist us.** The Company may make your non-public personal information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage the Software or provide Software content, advertisements and other services. Examples of such services include, without limitation: advertising and marketing, developing or supporting products and features, processing payments, processing data or statistics, and supplementing or organizing information or data. These outside service providers are required to protect non-public personal information entrusted to them and not use it for unauthorized purposes. 

**To contact you.** The Company may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to the Software to any email address you may have provided to us or periodic alerts on your mobile device if requested by you. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each promotional email or other method of notification. 

**To deliver relevant advertising.** We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of the Software through tracking and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant advertisements, offers and content when you use the Software. We may work with third party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you. We may share non-personally identifiable or aggregated information with third parties to improve the relevancy of the ads and content you see using the Software. This may involve transferring such information to servers that are located in the United States. As noted above, these third party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and other technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as aggregated information, demographic information, interests, affiliations, website usage, e-commerce, and other online activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. They may also utilize supplemental data from other sources and analytics methods to help deliver more relevant ads. To find out more about third party online advertising and to opt out of this type of advertising, visit the following websites: 

Digital Advertising Alliance: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

Network Advertising Initiative: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**To protect the rights of the Company and our users.** There may be instances when the Company may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where the Company has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of the Company, our affiliated companies, or any of their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of individuals; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process. 

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If the Company sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, the Company may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction. 

### 4\. MODIFICATIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy is the means by which the Company provides you with notice about its collection and use of your personal information. The Company may modify this Privacy Policy at any time upon notice to you, including but not limited to posting on the Company website containing this Privacy Policy or through the use of the Software. All material modifications will apply prospectively only. 

### 5\. DISCLAIMERS

**Third Party Advertisements and Links.** The Company is not affiliated with or responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties who advertise or link to any websites, products, services or offers through the Software, including but not limited to any reward programs, contests, sweepstakes, surveys, questionnaires, memberships, subscriptions, or trial offers. Once you click on an advertisement or link, you should carefully review the applicable privacy policy of such third party service or site. 

**Security.** Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet can ever be guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. The Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal information transmitted to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. If you believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify us of the problem and uninstall the Software immediately. 

### 6\. USER CONTROL AND UNINSTALLING SOFTWARE

You may uninstall the Software at any time by following the instructions provided in the End User License Agreement. Note that after you uninstall the Software, certain related files may remain on your system. These remnant files are a record of your previous download and are not executable programs. These files help to prevent fraud and to better service you if you choose to download the Software again. 

### 7\. LOCATION OF DATA

The Software is hosted in the United States and the Company is based in the United States. If you are a user located outside of the U.S., you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to, processed, and stored in the U.S. and other countries where data protection and other privacy laws may not offer the same level of protection as in your jurisdiction, such as the European Union. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above. 

### 8\. CONTACT US

If you have any questions or wish to contact us about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at: [privacy@getwebcake.com](mailto:privacy@getwebcake.com).
